<?php header('Content-type: text/xml'); ?> 

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#quotescenter">
		<br />
		<div class="raisedBox">
		<div style="padding:1%">
		<h3>Services</h3>

		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Database modeling and management</b><br />
			Collecting information about your customer base, or membership, is a vital tool. Expectially for targeting forward
			movement within your organization. We can build the tools necessary for you to succeed. The real benefits come over
			time being able to uncover trends that previously were undetected. the real leverage in database management is in the 
			questions you ask.
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Mobile Optimization</b><br />
			Sure your web site looks good on the desktop. However, whenever I direct a client to my site from their phone
			it becomes a haze of expanding and scrolling, ultimately clicking on unintended links and such. We'll take your site
			an maximize it's visibility for you when your with a client. This un-teathers you from your desk/lap top and
			leaves you to meet your customers where they are.
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>E-Commerse</b><br />
			If you have something to sell. We can put a shopping cart right on your site allowing you to move your product or 
			service in real time.
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Social Media Integration (targeted brand placement)</b><br />
			Social media is definitely changing the way we live and interact. More and more advertising is happening, not so much
			in "ads". Advertising is happening the old fashioned way again. Word of mouth. Social media helps in that endeavour in 
			that Brands are becoming more reconisable, and trusted based on the amount of "friends" that like that brand as well.
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Web Analyitics</b><br />
			Now that your new website is up and running. Who is viewing your site? What pages are being viewed? Where are these people located?
			When are these pages being viewed? How long to they stay on each page and or your site? Why do they come to your site. 
			The point being that the more information you have about your customer base, the better you can reach them. The more
			targeted your advertising becomes. 
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Web / server system maintenance</b><br />
			Wheather it be remote systems on a shared server. Or a fully dedicated system internally. We will help you maintain existing applications,
			help you in adding new applications. And maintain all server software on your system. We have extensive experience in both Windows 
			environments as well as Linux, and Unix's. 
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Web site development</b><br />
			we will take your idea and turn it into reality. Our focus is as always intuitive usability, coupled with style and excellence. You 
			can take part in as little or as much of the maintenance process as you like. 
		</div>
		<div class="row" style="padding-bottom:2%">
			<b>Code debugging / re-engineering</b><br />
			We have extensive experience in taking a brittle existing codebase and finding / fixing bugs. We can take your existing codebase and redesign
			with re-usability in mind. this saves on development, maintenance, and future development costs putting you in control.
		</div>
		</div>
		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
