

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#presentation">

		<div class="style5" style="width:100%">
			<img width="650" height="34" alt="Quality. Customized Approach. Luxury Living." src="/img/upland-homeinc/Quality_hdr.gif" />
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle" style="background-color:#860C17;">
			<span style="padding-left:5px; padding-top:10px; padding-right:6px;padding-bottom:6px" class="style8wide">Community
 			Information </span>
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle">
                      <p>
			Turn down Kirklands' dramatic boulevard entrance and know you have arrived at someplace special. 
			Beyond its brick and limestone walls and shimmering ponds lies an extraordinary atmosphere of elegance 
			and beauty. Here, generous homesites embrace award-winning home designs to reflect your high standards 
			and individuality.A rolling landscape, and winding streets balance privacy, 
			tranquility and an unmistakable sense of community. Kirklands' unique ambiance combines 
			innovation with an old-fashioned sense of community to create a setting most would be thrilled to call home.
                      </p>
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle">
                      <p class="style8wideBrown">Outstanding Included Features…                      </p>
                      <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Neighborhood Advantages</span><br />
                      • Acclaimed Rochester Community Schools<br />
                      • Dramatic Boulevard Entrance<br />
                      • Shimmering Ponds<br />
                      • Rolling Landscape with Winding Streets<br />
                      • Minutes from Downtown Rochester</p>

                      <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Your Home's Elegant Exteriors</span><br />
                      • Distinctive Architectural Designs<br />
                      • IKO Cambridge Dimensional Shingle<br />
                      • Roof Ridge Ventilation System<br />
                      • HardiPlank Fiber-Cement Siding with a Limited LifetimeWarranty<br />
                      • House Wrap to Reduce Air and Moisture Infiltration<br />
                      • Sherwin-Williams Solid Stain for Exterior Trim in Your Choice of Color<br />
                      • Aluminum Gutters and Downspouts<br />
                      • Therma-Tru Fiberglass Entry Doors with Weatherstrip<br />
                      • Jeld-Wen Vinyl Windows<br />
                      • Raised Panel Steel Sectional Garage Door <br />
                      • Concrete Driveway and Sidewalks<br />
                      • Two Exterior Electrical Outlets<br />
                      • Two Exterior Hose Bibss<br />
                      • Decorative Exterior Lighting</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Your Home’s Extraordinary Interiors</span><br />
                      • Dramatic Architectural Ceiling Details - per plan<br />
                      • 4” Crown Molding Included on First Floor<br />
                      • 4-1/2” Base Trim Detail Throughout<br />
                      • Decora Electrical Switches Throughout <br />
                      • Recessed Lighting Package - per plan <br />
                      • Decorative Light Fixtures with Your Choice of Satin Nickel or Oil Rubbed Bronze <br />
                      • Overhead Lights Included in All Bedrooms<br />
                      • Smooth Masonite Doors with Several Raised Panel Styles to Choose<br />
                      • Better Home Products, Pacific Heights, Door Hardware in Your Choice of 	Satin Nickel or Oil Rubbed Bronze <br />
                      • Wrought Iron Spindles Throughout<br />
                      • Sherwin-Williams Paint in Your Choice of Color<br />
                      • Ceramic or Hardwood flooring in Foyer and Select Areas - per plan<br />
                      • Lennox Gas Fireplace with Ceramic Surround</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Lavishly Appointed Kitchens</span><br />
                      • Granite tops with under-mount double stainless steel sink<br />
                      • Oversized Granite kitchen island - per plan<br />
                      • KraftMaid Maple custom cabinetry with dovetail drawers including full extension, self-closing drawer system<br />
                      • Your choice of Glasbern flooring in your choice of stain colors<br />
                      • 3-1/4" Oak hardwood flooring in your choice of stain colors<br />
                      • Prep fro gas and electric appliances<br />
                      • Hood vent prep to exterior<br />
                      • Insinkerator brand Badger 1 disposal<br />
                      • Delta Windemere kitchen sink faucet in Chrome or oil rubbed Bronze finish<br />
                      • Sun-drenched kitchen breakfast nook</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Luxurious Bath Retreats</span><br />
                      • Jacuzzi brand soaking tub in Master bath<br />
                      • Choice of white or biscuit plumbing fixtures<br />
                      • Delta windemere two handle bath faucets<br />
                      • Granite top bath vanities with under-mount sink - per plan<br />
                      • Full width vanity mirrors<br />
                      • Ceramic tile in full baths<br />
                      • Lavishly designed full ceramic master bath shower area<br />
                      • KraftMaid maple custom cabinetry with dovetail drawers including full extensions, self-closing drawer system<br />
                      • Custom designed hanging and shelving system in master suite walk-in closets</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">First Class Structurals &amp; Mechanical</span><br />
                      • 8'-10" Basement increased wall height<br />
                      • Basement waterproofing with dimple air gap membrane system including a 30 year limited warranty<br />
                      • American brand 50 gallon power vent water heater<br />
                      • AdvanTech subflooring with transferable 50 year limited warranty<br />
                      • Lennox 93% high efficiency forced air furances with 5 year limited warranty<br /> 
                      • 200 amp electrical service<br />
                      • Multiple hard-wired smoke detectors with battery back-up<br />
                      • 6 preps fro phone or cable<br />
                      • Security system prep</p>
		</div>

	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
