

<taconite>

	<replaceContent select="#topPicture">
		<center>
			<img src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/why-us.jpg" height="400" width="1200" alt="Why us" />
		</center>
	</replaceContent>
	<replaceContent select="#quotecenterleft">
		<br />
		<div style="padding:1%;">
			<div class="headline">Executive Cleaning Solutions is the right choice for you</div><br /><br />


			What drives us to be the best in this very competitive industry? Executive 
			Cleaning Solutions is driven by our commitment to customer service. We have 
			found over the years that our customer service and client satisfaction results 
			in long term relationships.   You will not have to worry about juggling cleaning 
			companies once you have Executive Cleaning Solutions inside your facility.  
			This always you to focus on your job, while we focus on keeping your work environment clean.  
			<br /><br />
			Executive Cleaning Solutions can help you reduce your workload. Not only can we ensure a clean 
			facility, but we can handle your supply ordering (soap, toilet paper, etc.), floor maintenance, 
			windowing cleaning, along with other services. By using us as a <b>“one stop shop”</b>, 
			you will not have to be concerned about all these stressors. 
			<br /><br />
			Our statistics show, on an average we maintain our clients for over five years. 
			We are proud of this measurable, as it shows that our <b>rates are competitive, 
			the service is exceptional</b> and our clients <b>appreciate</b> the <b>staff</b> we employ. 
			By contacting Executive Cleaning Solutions today, we will begin working towards a 
			cleaning plan that is conducive to your needs.
			<br /><br />
			<b>What we provide</b>
			<br />
			<ul>
				<li>An effective plan to ensure your facility is clean based on your requirements</li>
				<li>Superior service from our highly trained and friendly staff</li>
				<li>We use “green” supplies and environment friendly equipment</li>
				<li>Flexibility and commitment </li>
			</ul>


		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
