

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#presentation">

		<div class="style5" style="width:100%">
			<img width="650" height="34" alt="Quality. Customized Approach. Luxury Living." src="/img/upland-homeinc/Quality_hdr.gif" />
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle" style="background-color:#860C17;">
			<span style="padding-left:5px; padding-top:10px; padding-right:6px;padding-bottom:6px" class="style8wide">Community
                      Information </span>
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle">
                      <p>
			Turn down Century Oaks dramatic boulevard entrance and know you have arrived at someplace special. 
			Beyond this entrance lies an extraordinary atmosphere of elegance 
			and beauty. Here, generous homesites embrace award-winning home designs to reflect your high standards 
			and individuality. A rolling landscape, and winding streets balance privacy, 
			tranquility and an unmistakable sense of community. Century Oaks unique ambiance combines 
			innovation with an old-fashioned sense of community to create a setting thrilling to call home.
                      </p>
		</div>
		<div class="style5 tableStyle">
                      <p class="style8wideBrown">Outstanding Included Features…                      </p>
                      <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Neighborhood Advantages</span><br />
                      • Acclaimed Rochester Community Schools<br />
                      • Dramatic Boulevard Entrance<br />
                      • Rolling Landscape with Winding Streets<br />
                      • Minutes from Downtown Rochester</p>

                      <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Your Home's Elegant Exteriors</span><br />
                      • Distinctive Architectural Designs<br />
                      • Beautiful Brick Exteriors<br />
                      • Estate Sized Cul-de-sac Homesites<br />
                      • Dimensional Shingle with a Limited Lifetime Warrantee<br />
                      • Roof Ridge Ventilation System<br />
                      • DLP Siding with a Limited Lifetime Warrantee<br />
                      • House Wrap to Reduce Air and Moisture Infiltration<br />
                      • Sherwin-Williams Solid Stain for Exterior Trim in Your Choice of Color<br />
                      • Aluminum Gutters and Downspouts<br />
                      • Fiberglass Entry Doors with Weatherstrip<br />
                      • Jeld-Wen Vinyl Windows with Low-E Glass<br />
                      • Raised Panel Steel Sectional Garage Doors for 3 Car Garage <br />
                      • Concrete Driveway and Sidewalks with 3' Service Walk to Front Door<br />
                      • Two Exterior Electrical Outlets<br />
                      • Two Exterior Hose Bibss</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Your Home’s Extraordinary Interiors</span><br />
                      • Dramatic Architectural Ceiling Details - per plan<br />
                      • 4” Crown Molding Included on Formal Dining and Master Suite<br />
                      • 4-1/2” Base Trim Detail Throughout<br />
                      • Shaw Carpeting Throughout with 6 lb Pad<br />
                      • Decora Electrical Switches Throughout <br />
                      • Recessed Lighting Package - per plan <br />
                      • Generous Lighting Allomance<br />
                      • Overhead Lights Included in All Bedrooms<br />
                      • Smooth Masonite Doors with Raised Two-Panel Arch top Feature<br />
                      • Laundry Room with Ceramic Flooring - First or Second Floor per plan<br />
                      • Better Home Products, Pacific Heights, Door Hardware in Satin Nickel<br />
                      • Wrought Iron Spindles Throughout<br />
                      • Sherwin-Williams Paint in Your Choice of Color<br />
                      • 3/4"x2-1/4" Oak Stain Grade Hardwood Flooring in Foyer, Kitchen, <br />
                          Nook and Select Areas - per plan<br />
                      • Lennox Gas Fireplace with Ceramic Surround</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Lavishly Appointed Kitchens</span><br />
                      • Granite Tops with Under-Mount Double Stainless Steel Sink<br />
                      • Oversized Granite Kitchen Island - per plan<br />
                      • Quality Maple Custom Cabinetry with Gourmet Kitchen Layout <br />
                          and Crown Detail in Your Choice of Stain Color<br />
                      • 2-1/4" Stain Grade Oak Hardwood Flooring in Your Choice of Stain Colors<br />
                      • GE Appliance Package<br />
                      • Range Hood Vented to Exterior<br />
                      • Insinkerator Badger 1 Disposal<br />
                      • Delta Windemere Kitchen Sink Faucet in Chrome with Pullout Sprayer<br />
                      • Sun-drenched Kitchen Breakfast Nook</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">Luxurious Bath Retreats</span><br />
                      • Jacuzzi Brand Soaking Tub in Master Bath on Ceramic Tub Deck<br />
                      • Delta Windemere Chrome Two Handle Bath Faucets<br />
                      • Granite Top Bath Vanities with Under-Mount Sink - per plan<br />
                      • Full Width 36" Vanity Mirrors<br />
                      • Ceramic Tile Flooring in All Full Baths<br />
                      • Lavishly Designed Full Ceramic Master Bath Shower Area<br />
                      • Custom Designed Hanging and Shelving System in Master Suite Walk-in Closets</p>

                    <p><span class="style6BDkBrown">First Class Structurals &amp; Mechanical</span><br />
                      • 8'-10" Basement Increased Wall Height<br />
                      • Basement Waterproofing with Dimple Air Gap Membrane System <br />
                          Including a 30 Year Limited Warranty<br />
                      • American Brand 50 Gallon Power Vent Water Heater<br />
                      • AdvanTech Subflooring with Transferable 50 Year Limited Warranty<br />
                      • Carrier 95% High Efficiency Forced Air Furance with 5 Year Limited Warranty<br /> 
                      • 200 Amp Electrical Service<br />
                      • Multiple Hard-wired Smoke Detectors with Battery Back-up<br />
                      • 6 preps fro phone or cable<br />
                      • Security system prep</p>
		</div>

	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
