

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#topPicture">
                <center>
                        <img src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/service.jpg" alt="Services" height="400" width="1200" />
                </center>
        </replaceContent>

	<replaceContent select="#quotecenterright">
		<br />
		<div style="padding:1%;">
			24875 Novi Rd. #264<br />
			Novi, MI. 48376<br />
			(248)767-0976<br />
			<a href="mailto:erik@executive-cleaning-solutions.com?Subject=Executive-Cleaning-Solutions" class="nav">
				Customer Service</a><br /><br />
			<br /><br />
			<img height="384" width="322" src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/MichiganTriCountyMap.jpg" />
		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<replaceContent select="#quotecenterleft">
		<br />
		<div style="padding:1%;">

			If your location requires a Day Porter, Executive Cleaning Solutions will provide your 
			facility with a full or part -time professional and dependable Porter. Our staff will 
			be trained to your facility and have a complete understanding of all the cleaning 
			requirements needed. Our Day Porter will give you the peace of mind that your cleaning 
			needs are met in a timely manner. This will give you the freedom to focus on your business and cliental.
			<br /><br />

			Our Day Porters perform many invaluable duties to give your facility a professional 
			appears and an overall clean work environment. Whether it’s cleaning restrooms, event 
			preparation or floor maintenance, our experienced, dedicated and highly trained Day 
			Porter staff is here to service your facility.    
			<br /><br /><br />

			Some of the services our Day Porters provided:
			<ul>
				<li>Emptying and relining trash containers.</li>
				<li>Vacuuming carpeted areas</li>
				<li>Floor maintenance </li>
				<li>Shampooing carpets</li>
				<li>Cleaning kitchen area, appliances and food service preparation areas</li>
				<li>Cleaning elevators </li>
				<li>Cleaning common areas, break rooms, dusting and wiping down furniture </li>
				<li>Cleaning common and private bathrooms, refilling toilet paper, paper towels and soap </li>
				<li>Dusting </li>
				<li>Keep campus free from trash and refuse </li>
				<li>Movement of office furniture</li>
				<li>Assisting in setting-up conference areas, tables, chairs and equipment 
					for meeting rooms and special events</li>
				<li>All related custodial duties as required </li>
			</ul>
			<br /><br />

			Call Executive Cleaning Solutions today to discuss a plan that would work best for your facility.

		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
