

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#topPicture">
                <center>
                        <img src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/service.jpg" alt="Services" height="400" width="1200" />
                </center>
        </replaceContent>

	<replaceContent select="#quotecenterright">
		<br />
		<div style="padding:1%;">
			24875 Novi Rd. #264<br />
			Novi, MI. 48376<br />
			(248)767-0976<br />
			<a href="mailto:erik@executive-cleaning-solutions.com?Subject=Executive-Cleaning-Solutions" class="nav">
				Customer Service</a><br /><br />
			<br /><br />
			<img height="384" width="322" src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/MichiganTriCountyMap.jpg" />
		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<replaceContent select="#quotecenterleft">
		<br />
		<div style="padding:1%;">

		You deserve to walk into an immaculately clean facility when you arrive to work. 
		Executive Cleaning Solutions promises that you will appreciate the cleanliness of your 
		facility and also our highly trained staff. 
		<br /><br />

		Many have asked, what is the benefit of outsourcing your cleaning service? Simply said, 
		cleaning is what we do!  You can focus on your work and do not have to worry about who is 
		going to clean the bathroom or vacuum the floors. We will take care of all your office cleaning needs, 
		promise!  There is a saying "You never get a second change to make a first impression". 
		You want your employees, customer and guests to be in an environment that shows you care.
		<br /><br />

		Executive Cleaning Solution offers:<br />
		<ul>
			<li>Around the clock operational support</li>
			<li>Flexible cleaning plans to fit your needs</li>
			<li>Restocking</li>
			<li>Incredible staff that will dedicate themselves to your facility</li>
		</ul><br />

		If you’re a management company looking for a cleaning provider to service multiple locations 
		or a single property owner, Executive Cleaning Solutions is the best choice for you.  
		Simply call us or complete the “get a quote” information and we will discuss the best plan that will work for you.
		<br /><br />

		<img src="/img/executive-cleaning-solutions/servicesOfficeCleaningMidLeft.jpg" height="400" width="300" /><br />

		</div>
		<br />
	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
