

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#presentation">
		

	<div class="outerShell" style="display:block;zoom:1;">
	  <div id="content1">
	    <div style="display:block;">
	      <div style="display:block;text-align:left;">
		<br />
		Upland Homes was founded on a basic premise - build extraordinary homes that meet the high standards
		homeowners expect in luxury living. The Upland team is committed to delivering quality construction, creating practical,
		inviting floor plans and offering the opportunity to choose a home that best represents your personal style. We help you
		select the best property from our available sites, walk you through the design process and oversee every aspect of the
		building process. We will ensure your home includes all possible amenities. We serve as guide for both trade professionals 
		and homeowners. We guarantee a pleasant and compelling building experience.<br />
		<br />
		Our high standard of excellence in quality craftsmanship and extraordinary service has made Upland a 
		leading custom home builder in Michigan since the company was founded. We build with honesty, integrity and a solid commitment
		to quality. We never sacrifice quality for profit. In fact, our homes generate revenue due to the reputation we have earned.<br />
		<br />
		Upland has always sought out the finest local architects, contractors and support staff. This enables us to be
		one of Michigan's most respected builders. We use the latest in design technology and green building practices - on the forefront
		of innovation. Our designs vary from simple to simply spectacular. Give your home the extra special attention that will make it
		spectacular. Add your personal touch or let one of our experienced designers create the home you have envisioned. Select exactly
		the touch you want, or just be inspired. From fixtures to fountains, countertops to covered patios, you'll find it! You will
		have so much fun, you will never want to stop.<br />
		<br />
		The Upland team continues our commitment to you! We welcome a preview at one of our information centers to learn more 
		about Upland Homes. One of our knowledgeable representatives will help you find a home that is right for you.
		<div style="clear:both;"><br /></div>
	      </div>
	    </div>
	  </div>
	</div>


	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
