

<taconite>
	<replaceContent select="#presentation">



	<table width="100%" cellspacing="0" cellpadding="0" border="0">
            <tbody><tr>
              <td class="style5"><div><img width="468" height="34" alt="Quality. Customized Approach. Luxury Living." src="/img/upland-homeinc/Quality_hdr.gif" /></div>                </td>
            </tr>
            <tr>
              <td class="style5"><table bgcolor="#860C17" align="center" width="455" cellspacing="2" cellpadding="2" border="0">
                <tbody><tr>
                  <td><span style="padding-left:5px; padding-top:10px; padding-right:6px;padding-bottom:6px" class="style8wide">Ready
                      to Own Homes </span></td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                  <td bgcolor="#FFFFFF"><div class="style5" style="padding-left:9px; padding-top:1px; line-height:14px; padding-right:6px; padding-bottom:6px">
                      <p class="style3Link">Homesite #13</p>
                    <p>    • Floorplan - Windsor <br />
                         • 1700 Square Feet</p>
                    <p class="style6">THIS SMART RANCH DESIGN FEELS OPEN AND
                      AIRY WITH ITS VAULTED GREAT ROOM, DINING ROOM AND FOYER.
                      THE SECLUSION OF THE MASTER SUITE FROM THE REST OF THE
                      HOME ADDS TO THE FEELING OF SPACE IN THIS HOME. IF YOU
                      ARE LOOKING FOR MORE SPACE, WE CAN FINISH THE WALKOUT LOWER
                      LEVEL TO DOUBLE THE SQUARE FOOTAGE. STILL TIME TO CUSTOMIZE
                      THIS UNIQUE HOME TO YOUR PREFERRED FINISHES.</p>
                  </div></td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                  <td bgcolor="#FFFFFF"><div class="style5" style="padding-left:9px; padding-top:1px; line-height:14px; padding-right:6px; padding-bottom:6px">
                      <p class="style3Link">Homesite #14 </p>
                    <p>   • Floorplan - Ellington <br />
                         • 2351 Square Feet </p>
                    <p class="style6">ON THE FOUNDATION OF A WALKOUT LOWER LEVEL,
                      THIS CREATIVE DESIGN FEATURES A DUAL STAIRCASE, BUTLERS
                      PANTRY OFF DINING, OPEN AIRY GOURMET KITCHEN WITH GRANITE
                      COUNTERS, HARDWOOD FLOORS, AN ADJOINING GREAT ROOM WITH
                      FIREPLACE AND 9FT CEILING. A STUNNING PRIVATE LIBRARY ROUNDS
                      OUT THE FIRST FLOOR. SECOND FLOOR LAUNDRY. A MASTER SUITE
                      DESIGNED AS A RETREAT. 3 ADDITIONALL BEDROOMS COMPLETE
                      THIS BEAUTIFUL
                      HOME. </p>
                  </div></td>
                </tr>
                <tr>
                  <td bgcolor="#FFFFFF"><div class="style5" style="padding-left:9px; padding-top:1px; line-height:14px; padding-right:6px; padding-bottom:6px">
                      <p class="style3Link">Homesite #15</p>
                    <p>    • Floorplan - Clairmont <br />
                         • 2096 Square Feet</p>
                    <p class="style6">THE CREATIVE DESIGN OF THIS ELEGANT RANCH
                      HOME WILL BE SURE TO ENHANCE EVEN THE MOST SELECTIVE HOME
                      BUYERS LIFESTYLE. 12 FT CEILINGS, 2 SIDED FIREPLACE NESTLED
                      BETWEEN THE GREAT ROOM AND SPACIOUS GOURMET KITCHEN. A
                      BUTLERS PANTRY OFF DINING ROOM. THE RETREAT STYLE MASTER
                      SUITE FEATURES HIS AND HER WALK IN CLOSETS, TRAY CEILING AND
                      BEAUTIFUL BATH WITH LARGE SOAKING TUB AND SEPARATE SHOWER.</p>
                  </div></td>
                </tr>
                
              </tbody></table></td>
            </tr>
          </tbody></table>



	</replaceContent>

	<eval><![CDATA[
	]]></eval>
</taconite>
